9th Asia trusted life agents and
advisers
Awards thank you a for today's
award this year I am finally the winner
last year I was also a finalist but I
missed it by a little bit and I guess
this is what we talk about hard work
it's about consistency is about hard
work and I would like to ask every one
of you to give another round of applause
to all the finalists here
today I only have a few minutes so I'll
go a little bit faster I'm incredibly
humbled and proud to be standing on
stage today and you may notice that at
my table on the left hand side it
consists not of the usual industry
practitioners but really there are there
are two uh elderly people they are my
parents my father and mother are with me
today so are my two young youngest My
Two children CLA and Ken and my sister
jayen as well I did a career switch
exactly 7 years ago in July
2017 searching out from the global HR
Director to move into the industry
wasn't an easy decision but I'm glad
today I'm very very proud to say that I
made the right decision all this years
when I started this journey I was like a
baby my mentor was like a single dad
said he rolled up his sleeves and showed
me the way to the top of credential and
today at the top of this award as well
thank you my boss jayen he's standing
over there without persist without my
leader who persistently tried to recruit
me for many many many weeks I wouldn't
be standing here today and then as I
started to crawl and walk like a baby
you know as a child we grow up there
were many people that I learned from and
I know some of them are not here today
still I would like to show my greatest
appreciation to mentors like Mr Michael
xia Mr Chang kanglong Mr Albert SE and
even Mr Samuel go who sited there
today and then I was told by this Mentor
jine what you have achieved in the last
few years is what people could have
taken many years to achieve and for that
I'm very thankful to all their mentors
um mentoring and
teaching today Mr Jensen SE who let me
out of my lowest point in 201 19 when I
had to undergo a divorce is also remains
as a good friend of mine thank you
Jensen finally we have this gentleman
who is standing there my strategic coach
and my own client Mr Benjamin low he was
the one who paved my way from a rookie
all the way to where I am standing here
and winning this award today and also
the digital digital asent of the Year
leader of the year in 2022 is really
your doing you have created all this
wins for me I only did the work but you
did the magic thank you
Ben lastly a shout out to my sister
jayen also my team member also my mdrt
qualifier thank you for being here today
and always working this journey with me
if not without for you and I wouldn't be
able to skill so quickly and lastly to
my two children CL and kjun Mommy only
wants to tell you do your best in
whatever you do in your coming psle and
examinations
sometimes yeah I'm still a mother
sometimes the journey seems tough but
only tough times can make all of us
stronger comfort zone will only take us
away further away from our dreams and
goals and lastly allow me to
congratulate my own son kjun he won the
gold medal for his batminton na in the
national school games he's very proud to
he wants me to announce everybody thank
you so much
[Music]